<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:ror="http://rorweb.com/0.1/" >
<channel>
  <title>ROR Sitemap for http://www.cinnamonbreed.com/</title>
  <link>http://www.cinnamonbreed.com/</link>

<item>
     <link>http://www.cinnamonbreed.com/index.html</link>
     <title>Ceylon Cinnamon | Cinnamon Breed | Home</title>
     <description>cinnamonbreed tradings is a Sri Lankan Exports Company who are producing, distributing and exporting pure Ceylon cinnamon products,
     the business was started in 1989 by D.S De Silva as a cinnamon collector. Now it’s operating in exports business Cinnamonbreed is one of the best Cinnamon growers and
     exporters in Sri Lanka. Now it’s operating in exporting to the other part of the world. Having been involved in the Ceylon Cinnamon trade for more than a 3 decade they
     come with valu</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod></ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>0</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.cinnamonbreed.com/about.html</link>
     <title>About Us</title>
     <description>Why cinnamonbreed special in cinnamon export industry. what ara the cinnamonbreed company have client feedbacks
and also Something Special About The cinnamonbreed. what are the cinnamonbreed following standards for processing and producing cinnamon.how we are
 best in ceylon cinnamon export. what are the pure ceylon cinnamon qualities. why ceylon cinnamon, who we are in ceylon cinnamon export industury </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod></ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.cinnamonbreed.com/products.html</link>
     <title>Cinnamon Wholesale and Retail</title>
     <description>Concentrating in Pure Ceylon Cinnamon, Breed cinnamon tradings produces a differentiated portfolio of pure spices
	 for export merchandise. We grade our true cinnamon with different sizes  and highly focusing on quality  with different needs of our valued clients.
	 We are produce and export several categories of Cinnamon wich are ALBA, 5C-SP, 5C, 4C, 5M, 4M, H1, H2, H2 FAQ,
	No 1 Quillings, No 2 Quillings, Cut Cinnamon, Cinnamon Powder, Cinnamon Leaves, Cinnamon Leaf Oil
	and also Cinnamon Bark</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod></ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.cinnamonbreed.com/gallery.html</link>
     <title>Our Gallery</title>
     <description>This is cinnamonbreed gallery, there is many photos how we are processing cinnamon, cut cinnamon, cinnamon powder,
and kind of cinnamon images,ALBA, 5C-SP, 5C, 4C, 5M, 4M, H1, H2, H2 FAQ, No 1 Quillings, No 2 Quillings,
 Cut Cinnamon, Cinnamon Powder, Cinnamon Leaves, Cinnamon Leaf Oil and Cinnamon Bark Oil</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod></ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.cinnamonbreed.com/contact.html</link>
     <title>Contact us</title>
     <description>If you have any queries or clarifications on cinnamon export services offered by the cinnamonbreed,
    please feel free to contact us these are cinnamonbreed tradings contact details,Message us.call us, mail us
    Your official source for 24/7 customer supports ,Just send us your questions or concerns
    by starting a new case and we will give you the help you need, contact via
     whats app(+94770770205),messenger,email,phone(+94770770205) and telephone(+94912264508) </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod></ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
  